brandingpersonality.com 2010-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Personal Marketing and Personal Branding Online

## Privacy Policy

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.

  * ## You are not logged in

You are not currently logged in.

Username:  
  
Password:  
  
Remember Me

» [Register]()  
» [Lost your Password?](http://www.brandingpersonality.com/wp-login.php?action=lostpassword)

  * ## Marieke Hensel, Owner Branding Personality

  * ## Mission Statement

**Branding Personality expresses the authentic voice of personal and consumer brands online to generate profits by rewarding your loyal customers and attracting new ones.**

  * ## Social Media Presence

  * ## 360 Reach Personal Brand Assessment Certified

  *   * ## Recent Posts

  * ## Community

Login with Facebook:

    * Visitors
    * Friends
    * Comments

Last visitors

Powered by [Sociable!](http://www.sociable.es/)

  * ## Testimonial

"Branding Personality has not only achieved **an immediate major sales increase of 800%** , the overall growth has risen to 300% as a direct result of the project. Hensel Hosting is sincerely grateful for the expert-knowledge and hands-on mentality, and the inspiration to achieve higher goals that cannot be expressed in money terms. Thank you!"  
\- Rutger Hensel, CEO [Hensel Hosting](http://www.henselhosting.com/)

  * ## Join Branding Personality

  * ## Free ebook ‘Attract your target market online’

FREE ebook on **How to attract your target market online** with your subscription to our monthly **Online Business Building** publication.  
First name:|   
---|---  
Primary email:|   
  
  * ## Location

122 N. Harbor Blvd #110  
Fullerton, CA 92832  
USA  

© 2006–2007 Personal Marketing and Personal Branding Online — [Sitemap](http://www.brandingpersonality.com/sitemap.xml) — [Design](http://cutline.tubetorial.com/) by [Henselutions](http://www.henselutions.com/) — hosted by [Hensel Hosting](http://www.henselhosting.com/)

Powered by WishList Member - [Membership Software](http://member.wishlistproducts.com/ "Membership Site Software")

Privacy Policy | Security Policy | Refund Policy
